asiancrush.com 2019-11-07

# PRIVACY POLICY | AsianCrush

**Features of the use of steroids.**  Every modern person has to decide for himself how he sees his own body and what he wants to achieve with the help of balanced nutrition and training. Since many of us are maximalists, we are used to set high goals. These are the athletes who strive to do everything faster or more [buy anabolic steroids](http://liquidroids.com/ "buy anabolic steroids") efficiently than their rivals in the competition. It is impossible to achieve such a result without a comprehensive approach. In order not to have to regret not quite an impressive result, it is better to combine grueling exercises with taking special drugs that can improve their effectiveness.

**Achieving a lofty goal.**  Today, anabolic steroids are a common type of pharmacology that athletes take. These drugs allow you to beat the competition and to install put before you. It is only necessary not to forget about the rules and doses of their use to minimize the risk of negative factors. High-quality sports pharmacology makes it possible to make the muscles more dense, as well as to increase the relief of the body.

## Anabolic steroids

The use of such drugs in the modern world is not a novelty. They have been known for several decades, so more than one generation of athletes was able to achieve excellent results through their use. A bodybuilder just needs to know where to buy steroids. Such products are offered by many companies today, but only some of them can guarantee really high quality of the presented products. Correct dosage of these drugs will help at all to eliminate the side effects. If you need a first-class sports pharmacology, feel free to contact us and get the opportunity to purchase such substances. With their help, the body will be maintained in perfect condition without harm.

**Variety of drugs.**  The use of special means allows athletes to achieve important goals. Some athletes decide to buy steroids in order to increase muscle mass. Another use of drugs allows you to get rid of fatty tissues that interfere with the creation of a beautiful figure. To increase the weight, you should use:

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how AsianCrush, and its affiliated entities, Asian Media Rights, and Digital Media Rights, uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.  
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over those linked website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to each website visited.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@asiancrush.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting.  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us at support@asiancrush.com. We will correct any information found to be incorrect.
